playcomet.com 2019-08-31

# privacy policy - PlayComet.com

This is the privacy policy of playcomet Inc. and any companies within our group . It applies to all of our websites / services (referred to collectively as "our websites") on which it appears.

Please read this policy carefully. Your accepting it in full is a condition of your use of our websites (whether or not you are a subscriber). If you do not agree with this policy, or any part, please do not use our websites. Your using any of our websites is treated as an acceptance of the version of this policy in effect at the time of your use. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us by emailing support(at)playcometgame.com and do not use our websites until you are satisfied and can accept this policy in its entirety.

We are committed to protecting your privacy and take special measures to ensure the confidentiality of personally identifiable information collected from or about you. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store and use such personally identifiable information. ("Personally identifiable information" is information that identifies you and can be used to contact or locate you in real life, such as your real full name, e-mail address, mobile telephone number, postal address.)  
References to "Terminating" an account include all or any of: locking / suspending, temporarily banning or permanently banning the account.

**What personal information is collected?**

playcomet only collects personal information on a voluntary basis. If an on-line visitor submits information to playcomet, it will usually take the form of either: (1) the purchase of goods or services though our on-line stores, (2) product or account registration, or registration for on-line game participation, (3) player match-up services, (4) message boards, (5) warranty registrations, (6) contest registrations, (7) a consumer complaint, (8) surveys, (9) customer service or technical support, and/or (10) newsletters. Personal information collected may include your name, home address, phone number, and/or e-mail address. We do not require this information to gain access to our sites, however, you will not be able to utilize certain products, services, or features that require registration or receive materials such as newsletters unless such information is provided.  
Visitors purchasing products or services through our on-line stores will be required to provide additional information such as a valid credit card number, expiration date, and shipping and billing addresses.

Please note that, depending on the playcomet site that you are visiting, many of the activities listed above may not be available and, as such, personal information may not be collected.

**What other information is collected and stored?**

We use cookies, collect and store IP-addresses, alphanumeric IDs and other unique identifiers in order to identify specific computers that access our websites. We identify and store the versions of Java and .NET (if any) on your computer along with your browser and operating system.  
We generate and store logs indicating usage of our websites such as activity in our games and public and private chat communications. This includes monitoring play patterns and anti-tamper checks which verify the correct internal operation of our software and are designed to spot abusive or inappropriate activities.  
We may track your use of certain features and areas of our websites to help us improve them.  
If our client software held on your computer fails, it sends an automatic error report to our server to help us fix it. This error report only includes information about the internal state of our own client software and which browser/java version it is running on. It does not include data from elsewhere on your system and so does not reveal personally identifiable information to us.  
We store 'save game' and 'game settings' information to enable us to provide a better games service in which your activities and achievements are remembered in the game, and we conduct polls to find better ways of serving the needs of our users.

**Children's privacy practices of playcomet**

The provision of playcomet Products to anyone under 18 years of age is not conditioned on the collection of more personal information than is reasonably necessary for participation.

**How We Use Your Information provided/collected?**

The information we collect may be used:  
i. To provide our customer support service, and to verify any claims or requests you make if you use our customer support service.  
ii. To enforce our terms and conditions, and prevent or detect hacking activities, security breaches or safety risks in connection with our websites.  
iii. To send service announcements and messages (for example, a reminder sent to the members' Message Centre if a subscription payment is due or if member credit has expired).  
iv. To aggregate information to generate anonymous statistics regarding use of our websites. We may share this anonymous information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
v. For our own internal marketing and demographic studies and to help us improve our websites.  
vi. In the event of an actual or proposed (including as part of negotiations for any) merger, or business combination or sale of substantially all of our assets or a business operation to which such information relates, or as provided under bankruptcy or applicable insolvency laws or by the enforcement of equitable rights.  
vii. To disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government, regulatory or law enforcement authority, to protect or assist in protecting our users, systems or the public, or to otherwise enforce legal rights as determined in our sole and absolute discretion.  
viii. If you have agreed on our websites, to send you email newsletters about our games, including new game features and special offers.  
ix. As set out elsewhere in our privacy policy.  
We care about protecting your privacy, and with the exception of the uses specified above, we will not sell, transfer, rent out, share or disclose your personally identifiable information to other companies.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.  
Session cookies are temporary, and remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site. We use session cookies to enable us to authenticate users during game sessions.  
Persistent cookies remain in the cookie file of your browser for a specific period. Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you.  
We use persistent cookies to track your country (to enable us to provide country-specific content) and to track whether you entered our websites from a link on site of one of our business partners. Persistent cookies also allow you to login when you return to our site, by storing your login information on your own computer. Additionally we may use persistent cookies to store information about which adverts from our site have been displayed to you to help avoid showing the same one repeatedly or to provide information that we hope will meet your needs or interests.  
Our advertisers and technology partners also use cookies and other similar technologies. For more information about this, see under "Third Parties" below.

**Third Parties**

We may supply your personal information to external third parties who provide a service to us (such as fulfillment of orders placed for playcomet Product merchandise or to assist us in the supply of customer support) and purely for the purpose of that service.  
We partner with a number of external payment service provider companies to enable you to make payment via a wide range of payment options. We share your billing information with such companies insofar as is necessary for the processing of your payment or to prevent or detect fraud. These companies have agreed not to retain, share, store or use your personally identifiable information which we pass to them for any secondary purposes.  
Please note that this privacy policy does not apply to any of your personal information which is collected by the external payment provider companies themselves or to the websites or services of other companies to which we link or which link to us, or which provide goods or services to our users from their websites (such as co-branded, white label or affiliate sites or other sites selling playcomet Product merchandise). Please note that those companies (and not playcomet) are responsible for the information which they collect. Please check their privacy polices where appropriate.  
We use external companies to provide and serve adverts or other technologies on our websites (eg to collect website statistics or to enable sharing of buttons or widgets). These companies may use information (not including personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to personalize advertisements on this site or other sites and /or to personalize certain features on our site and/or to provide anonymised aggregated statistics concerning use of our site or use of certain features on our site which are shared with other sites (eg buttons or widgets linking to our site). We do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies that these third parties may use and the information practices of these advertisers and technology companies are not covered by this policy.  
Furthermore, information collected from our users by third parties providing goods or services (including adverts) at or via our websites may be shared by those third parties with us and stored by us for the purposes stated in this policy.  
Be very careful before making or posting any communications on our websites. Certain information is visible to other players of the game including: public and private chat communications, the appearance of your characters and your experience points. Players who include you on their friends list can see which in-game world you are playing on.  
If you have agreed on our websites, we may provide your email address to our business partners so that they can send you emails with details of goods or services which may be of interest to you including information about special offers or promotions.

**Safeguarding your personally identifiable information**

We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent we believe it reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and will protect it using the same level of safeguards we use to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of our own equivalent proprietary information. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer any personally identifiable information in accordance with this policy will agree to provide sufficient protection. We may store or transfer personal information outside the European Economic Area for the purposes stated in this policy.  
Note that while we strive to protect all our personally identifiable information, we have all heard of data breaches in well-respected financial and governmental institutions and we cannot ever fully guarantee that such breaches will not happen. We will inform you of any material data breaches that we discover that may compromise your personally identifiable information.

**Transfer of Information**

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of playcomet or the acquisition of substantially all the assets of playcomet related to the business which collected such information, such as acquisition by or merger with another company.
